myxertones.com 2013-06-29

# Myxer - Privacy Policy

Myxer Inc ("Myxer", we, us) understands the importance of privacy and is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use your personal information through our myxer.com website. 

## WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Myxer collects personal information to improve the manner by which we operate and offer our products and services. We use the personal information to communicate with you about those products and services, and provide effective, timely customer support when needed. You can always opt out of receiving future marketing communications from us by following the instructions in the communication. From time to time, we may share your contact information with select third parties who we think have products or services that will be of interest to you. We will not share your personal information with anyone without your consent except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

Myxer collects information when you visit myxer.com pages, register with us through myxer.com, and when you use Myxer products or services. Note that there may be different privacy policies for different Myxer products, such as myxer.fm. 

  * The information may include your mobile phone number, name, email address, and information such as your birth year and zip code. 
  * If you decide to purchase content from us or sign up for a premium program, such as Mobile Artist PRO and Mobile Label PRO accounts, we may also ask for your billing information including your billing address. 
  * We automatically receive information on our server logs from your browser, including your computer configuration (such as operating system, connection speed, and peripherals); mobile phone device information and network carrier information and the Internet IP address and URL of the website that sent you to the Myxer registration page. 
  * We collect the types of peripherals used by Myxer products on your computer. 
  * We collect other optional profile data including but not limited to a display image. 
  * We collect demographic information provided by you (such as language, gender and age, and, if applicable, content preferences and personalization information). 
  * We collect location based information from your computer’s IP address and/or your GPS enabled phone. 
  * We also collect your musical usage patterns and types of music you listen to whether you logged into or out of a Myxer service, or if change your password or billing information. 

## HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?

Myxer uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). 

Google is one of the third-party advertising companies used to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

## HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Myxer uses your mobile phone number and mobile phone device information to deliver to you mobile phone content such as ringtones, full-track music downloads, pictures, and videos. 

Myxer uses your other personal information to deliver to you and bill you for Myxer products and services, and communicate with you concerning your account and customer service issues. This may include: 

  * verifying authorization of credit card usage before any purchase of premium content or services; 
  * updating you on important changes to your account such as the receipt of payments and thanks for inviting your friends. 
  * determining if you meet the minimum system requirements to use our products, and providing information concerning compatibility and interoperability to you; 
  * asking you to participate in surveys about products, services, news and events; 
  * offering you product upgrades, content and services for you to purchase; 
  * providing you with content, services, instructions, and a more personalized experience based on personal information, such as zip/postal code and any content or other preferences you provide; 
  * in the case of the Myxer Desktop Agent or any other downloaded Myxer software, auto-updating that downloaded Myxer software; 
  * providing you with news, free newsletters, updates, targeted advertising, promotions, and special offers that give you a better understanding of how our products are used. 

The information that makes up your "public profile" including the display name you choose to associate with your account, and an optional image you may have chosen to use to represent you, are public information that may be shared with others. In addition, information about what band "fanlists" you have joined, and what content you have recently contributed to or downloaded from Myxer are public by default. You may choose to hide this last bit of information by choosing the appropriate selections from the account preferences pages. 

## HOW DO WE HANDLE CHILDREN’S PRIVACY CONCERNS?

Myxer does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on any Myxer website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our websites is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Myxer websites or services at any time or in any manner. If Myxer learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Myxer websites without verified parental consent, then Myxer will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

## WHEN AND HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?

Myxer may disclose relevant information about our customers to our contractors (e.g. a customer service contractor or a credit card clearing service) in order for them to provide specific services for Myxer, and to better serve our customers. Myxer's contractors are bound by strict contractual requirements to keep all personal information they process strictly confidential and to use such information solely on behalf of Myxer. Also, Myxer may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

(a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Myxer;  
(b) protect and defend the rights or property of Myxer and its products; or   
(c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Myxer products or the public at large.  

From time to time, we may share your contact information with select third parties who we think have products or services that will be of interest to you. In addition, Myxer also may use and share non-personally identifiable information, such as general demographic or location information, mobile phone make or model, wireless carrier information, content preferences and content consumption data, or information about the computer or device from which you access the Service. The use and disclosure of such anonymous information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy. Myxer may share this information with its advertising and business partners in order to provide you with targeted advertisements and other offers which may interest you. Myxer may also enable these advertisers or business partners to ask you for personal information, with your consent, for the purpose of offering you access to their products or services. Also, in the event we sell or transfer any of the assets associated with myxer.com, this may include disclosure of your personal information to the purchasing entity. 

The Myxer websites and products may contain links to other websites and products. Myxer is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or products. Please visit the privacy policies of these sites in order to understand their privacy policies and data collection practices. 

If you do not want your contact information shared with any third parties, please email [support@myxer.com](mailto:support@myxer.com). 

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We may revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with Myxer products, services and web pages and do so with some regularity. Please revisit this policy to ensure that you understand and agree with how we collect and handle your personal information. 

## NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE

We customarily release alpha and beta versions of our products, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome feedback on any privacy concerns you may have, and on how to improve our products generally, in all stages of release. Myxer does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. Myxer shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the United States. 

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our products or services or would like to make a complaint, please contact: [support@myxer.com](mailto:support@myxer.com)

NOTE: mVisible®, Myxer®, MyxerTones®, MyxerTags™, MyxerCodes™, and MyxerPix™ are trademarks of Myxer Inc.  
Last modified: February 27th, 2013
